Guide to the Japan International Christian University Foundation, Inc. Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
Japan International Christian University Foundation, Inc. Records
1911-2011
RG 89
Yale University Divinity School Library
35
83 boxes
The records primarily document the operations and policies of the Japan International Christian University Foundation and also include documents generated by or descriptive of the International Christian University itself. The collection provides valuable evidence about the university as well as the cooperation between Japanese and American Christians that led to its creation and success. Of interest is documentation of JICUF as a church-related non-profit support agency, particularly the role of women in its work. Discussions to establish a Christian college in Japan began in 1945, only months after the bombings of Hiroshima and Nagasaki. In 1948, the original committee was dissolved into a legal foundation, the Japan Christian University Foundation, Inc., which provided significant early publicity and financial support, distributing academic materials, sponsoring Western faculty members and, later, coordinating alumni activities. In 1949, the constitution of the ICU was adopted and the first freshman class was admitted four years later. In 1957, the first graduate school, the School of Education, was opened. By the 1990s, ICU was a highly distinguished university with more than 2,000 students. Due to declining contributions, an increasingly large operations deficit, and related changes in its relationship with the university, JICUF closed its New York offices in 1991. The organization would have no offices or staff for five years and a minimal board of six members. The Othmer bequests in 1995 and 1998 as well as the university's 50th anniversary fundraising project revitalized JICUF activity and a new office in NY was opened in 1997. Between 1999 and 2001 JICUF was restructured into a program organization (The Japan ICU Foundation, Inc.) and an endowment organization (The JICUF Endowment, Inc.).
Japan International Christian University Foundation, Inc
Conditions Governing Access
Open to qualified researchers.
Biographical / Historical
Discussions that led to the establishment of The International Christian University in Tokyo, Japan began only months after the bombings of Hiroshima and Nagasaki. The discussions began with the board of trustees of Tokyo Woman's Christian College but soon included a larger group of Japanese Christian leaders. An American deputation sent to Japan in October, 1945 by the Federal Council of Churches of Christ in North America and the Foreign Missions Conference of North America joined the discussions and returned to America with the vision of facilitating the creation of a new Christian university in Japan.
The Federal Council and the Foreign Missions Conference formed a "Joint Committee for a Christian University in Japan" in March, 1947. While planning for the establishment of the university went on in Japan, the American committee developed a structure to provide advice and financial support. In January, 1948 the International Christian University Research Institute, an embyro form of the University, was inaugurated. In November, 1948 the Joint Committee was dissolved into a legal foundation, the Japan Christian University Foundation, Incorporated (the word "International" was inserted later).
On June 15, 1949 the constitution of the International Christian University was adopted and four years later the first freshman class was admitted to its College of Liberal Arts. In 1957 the first graduate school of the ICU, the School of Education, was opened. By the 1990s, ICU was a highly distinguished university with more than 2,000 students.(A full history of the university is available in Charles W. Iglehart's Intrenational Christian University - An Adventure in Christian Hihger Education in Japan, Tokyo: ICU, 1964).)
The Japan International Christian University Foundation, Inc. provided significant early publicity and financial support for the university, as well as distributing academic materials, sponsoring Western faculty members, and coordinating alumni activities.
Notable leaders of the Foundation are as follows:
Presidents /Chairs of Board of Trustees:
Ralph E. Diffendorfer 1948-1951
Kenneth S. Latourette 1951-1968
Andrew W. Cordier 1969-1975
David H. C. Read 1976-1990
Delores J. Roeder 2002-2011
Paul R. Gregory 1990-2000
David Vikner 2000-2002
Executive Directors and Executive Secretaries:
Thoburn T. Brumbaugh 1946-1958
Charles J. Turck 1958-1961
Henry Bovenkerk and Ruth Miller 1961-1964
Ruth Miller 1964-1982
Betty Gray 1983-1991
Dorothy Kinney 1997 (Interim Director)
Jiro Mizuno 1997-1999
Ching-fen Hsiao 2000-2002
David Vikner 2002-
The Foundation had its headquarters at 475 Riverside Drive in New York City. Due to declining contributions, an increasingly large operations deficit, and related changes in its relationship with the university, JICUF closed its New York offices in 1991. The organization would have no offices or staff for five years and a minimal board of six members. The Othmer bequests in 1995 and 1998 as well as the university's 50th anniversary fundraising project revitalized JICUF activity and a new office in NY was opened in 1997. Between 1999 and 2001 JICUF was restructured into a program organization (The Japan ICU Foundation, Inc.) and an endowment organization (The JICUF Endowment, Inc.).
Scope and Contents
I. Official Documents and Minutes
II. Organization and Personnel Records/ Correspondence
III. Events, Programs
IV. Financial and Fundraising Records
V. Publications/ Photographs
VI. ICU Buildings, Blueprints, and Property.
VII. Addendum 2012
While these records primarily document the operations and policies of the Japan International Christian University Foundation, they also include documents generated by or descriptive of the International Christian University itself. The record group provides valuable evidence about the university as well as the cooperation between Japanese and American Christians that led to its creation and success. The record group's thorough documentation of a church-related non-profit support agency is also of interest, particularly from the standpoint of the strong role of women in its work.
Series I provides the official definition of the Foundation, its policies, and programs, including legal documents and full sets of minutes for the various administrative and program entities within the Foundation.
Series II includes correspondence, proposals, reports, and other records documenting the formation and development of the Foundation, and its relationships with the ICU. An initial section of chronologically arranged documentation is followed by files arranged by administrative and program entities, and by individual names. The individual files represent officers and leaders of the Foundation, as well as of the ICU itself. Reports of the ICU Presidents are included in their individual files. Information about the decision to close the Foundation office in New York is available in the files for Kunio Oguchi and Philippa Hughes.
As is the case with many archives of organizations, there is considerable overlap among files and series. For example, documentation of the relationship between the Foundation and the ICU is available primarily in the historical material of Series II and the records of meetings and consultations in Series III, but can also be found within the individual files of Foundation and ICU leaders. It should also be noted that the extensive input of the executive directors of the Foundation, particularly Ruth Miller and Betty Gray, may not be immediately apparent from the finding aid. Suffice it to say that all these files were in some sense those of the executive directors of the Foundation.
The first section of Series III focuses on meetings and consultations related to the evolving relationship between the Foundation and the ICU. The remainder of the Series documents events and programs sponsored by the Foundation to provide publicity and financial support for the ICU. These events and programs, of course, were organized by the various committees and individuals of the Foundation, so there is overlap of documentation between Series I, II, and III.
The financial and fundraising records of Series IV are extensive because a major role of the Foundation was to provide financial support for the ICU. Financial documentation is also available in the Finance Committee minutes of Series I and in the individual files of financial officers in Series II.
The publications of Series V include newsletters, radio scripts, and brochures designed to engender support of the Foundation and the ICU. Copies of several articles about the ICU that appeared in church-related periodicals provide a good overview of the origins and philosophy of the university. The photographs in this series are in addition to those filed amidst the documentation of events and programs in Series III.
The records found in Series V are a rather eclectic mixture of documentation of the ICU campus. These items collected and retained by the Foundation office in New York undoubtedly represent a small sample of similar documentation available in the archives of the ICU in Japan.
The last series in an Addendum added to the collection in 2012.
Arrangement
I. Official Documents and Minutes
II. Organization and Personnel Records/ Correspondence
III. Events, Programs
IV. Financial and Fundraising Records
V. Publications/ Photographs
VI. ICU Buildings, Blueprints, and Property.
VII. Addendum 2012
Christian education -- Japan; Universities and colleges -- Japan; Japan International Christian University Foundation, Inc; Kokusai Kirisutokyō Daigaku
- Official Documents and Minutes, Series I
  Scope and Contents
  This series is divided into the following sections:
  Joint Committee for a Christian University in Japan
  Corporation of JICUF
  Board of Directors
  Executive Committee
  Finance Committee
  Investment Committee
  Men's Committee
  Executive Committee of the Women's Planning Committee
  Women's Planning Committee
  - Official Documents
    - JICUF Constitution and Bylaws, 1949-1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Amendment to JICUF Constitution, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Amendment to JICUF Constitution, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Certificate of Incorporation; Change of Name; Certificate of Amendment of the Certificate of Incorporation, 1949-1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Minutes
    - Joint Committee for a Christian University in Japan, 1946 Dec- 1948 Oct (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Joint Committee for a Christian University in Japan, 1946-1948 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Advisory Committees of the Joint Committee for a Christian University in Japan, 1948,1949 (Box 2, Folder 9a)
    - Trustees of ICU, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Corporation of JICUF, 1951-1976 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Corporation of JICUF, 1977-1991 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Board of Directors, 1948 Nov- 1949 Apr (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Board of Directors, 1949 Jul 25, 26 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Board Meeting Proceedings, 1949 Jul 25 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Board Meeting Proceedings, 1949 Jul 26 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Board of Directors, 1949 Oct-Nov (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Board of Directors, 1949 Dec- 1950 Jun (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Board of Directors, 1950 Jul- 1951 Jan (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Board of Directors, 1951 Jun- 1952 Jun (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Board of Directors, 1952 Oct- 1953 Jun (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Board of Directors, 1953 Oct- 1954 Oct (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Board of Directors, 1955 Jan-Oct (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Board of Directors, 1956 Jan-Jun (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Board of Directors, 1957 Oct- 1958 Jan (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Board of Directors, 1958 Jun- 1959 Jan (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Board of Directors, 1959 Jun- 1960 Jan (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Board of Directors, 1960 Jun- 1961 Oct (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Board of Directors, 1962 Jan-Oct (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Board of Directors, 1963 Jan- 1964 Jan (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Board of Directors, 1964 Jun- 1965 Oct (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Board of Directors, 1966 Jan- 1967 Jan (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Board of Directors, 1967 Jun- 1970 Jan (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Board of Directors, 1971 Jan- 1981 May (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Board of Directors, 1982 May- 1986 Jun (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Board of Directors, 1987 Jun- 1995 Jun (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Executive Committee, 1950 May- 1951 Jun (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Executive Committee, 1951 Sep- 1953 May (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Executive Committee, 1953 Jun- 1954 Dec (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Executive Committee, 1955 Jan-Oct (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Executive Committee, 1955 Nov- 1956 Nov (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Executive Committee, 1956 Dec- 1958 Mar (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Executive Committee, 1958 May- 1960 Jul (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Executive Committee, 1960 Sep- 1962 Dec (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Executive Committee, 1963 Jan- 1964 Dec (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Executive Committee, 1965 Feb- 1966 Jun (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Executive Committee, 1966 Jul- 1967 Dec (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Executive Committee, 1968 Jan- 1970 May (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Executive Committee, 1970 Jun- 1972 Dec (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Executive Committee, 1973 Mar- 1976 Mar (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Executive Committee, 1976 May- 1978 Jun (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Executive Committee, 1978 Sep- 1980 Nov (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Executive Committee, 1983 Jan- 1986 Sep (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Executive Committee, 1986 Nov- 1989 Apr (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Executive Committee, 1989 May- 1991 Mar (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Finance Committee, 1953 Jul- 1960 Dec (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Finance Committee, 1961 Feb- 1968 May (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Finance Committee, 1968 Jun- 1973 Oct (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - Finance Committee, 1974 Feb- 1979 Nov (Box 11, Folder 60)
    - Finance Committee, 1980 Oct- 1987 Nov (Box 11, Folder 61)
    - Finance Committee, 1988 Mar- 1991 Feb (Box 11, Folder 62)
    - Investment Committee, 1986 Apr- 1988 Mar (Box 11, Folder 63)
    - Men's Committee, 1963 Mar-Jun (Box 11, Folder 64)
    - Men's Committee, 1965 Sep- 1968 Nov (Box 12, Folder 65)
    - Men's Committee, 1968 Dec- 1973 May (Box 12, Folder 66)
    - Men's Committee, 1973 Sep- 1982 Jun (Box 12, Folder 67)
    - Men's Committee, 1982 Sep- 1990 Feb (Box 12, Folder 68)
    - Executive Committee of the Women's Planning Committee, 1953 Feb- 1956 Jun (Box 12, Folder 69)
    - Executive Committee of the Women's Planning Committee, 1956 Sep- 1958 Jan (Box 13, Folder 70)
    - Executive Committee of the Women's Planning Committee, 1958 Feb-Sep (Box 13, Folder 71)
    - Executive Committee of the Women's Planning Committee, 1958 Oct- 1959 Jul (Box 13, Folder 72)
    - Executive Committee of the Women's Planning Committee, 1959 Sep- 1961 Jun (Box 13, Folder 73)
    - Executive Committee of the Women's Planning Committee, 1961 Aug- 1963 Jul (Box 13, Folder 74)
    - Executive Committee of the Women's Planning Committee, 1963 Sep- 1965 Jun (Box 14, Folder 75)
    - Executive Committee of the Women's Planning Committee/ Women's Committee, 1967 Apr (Box 14, Folder 76)
    - Executive Committee of the Women's Committee, 1967 May- 1970 Dec (Box 14, Folder 77)
    - Executive Committee of the Women's Committee, 1970 Feb- 1974 Dec (Box 14, Folder 78)
    - Executive Committee of the Women's Committee, 1975 Jan- 1978 Dec (Box 14, Folder 79)
    - Executive Committee of the Women's Committee/ Women's Planning Committee, 1985 May (Box 14, Folder 80)
    - Women's Planning Committee, 1953 Jan- 1957 Oct (Box 15, Folder 82)
    - Women's Planning Committee, 1958 Jan- 1963 Jun (Box 15, Folder 83)
    - Women's Planning Committee/ Women's Committee, 1964 Jan- 1974 Apr (Box 15, Folder 84)
    - Women's Planning Committee/ Women's Committee, 1975 Apr- 1987 Dec (Box 15, Folder 85)
    - Women's Planning Committee, 1987 Feb- 1988 Dec (Box 15, Folder 86)
    - Women's Planning Committee, 1989 Mar 1991 Apr (Box 15, Folder 87)
- Organization and Personnel Records/Correspondence, Series II
  non-JICUF sponsored
  JICUF sponsored
  - JICUF/ICU History
    - Early proposals re. a Christian university in Japan, 1911, 1932, 1945 (Box 16, Folder 88)
    - Reports and Resolutions, 1946-1948 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Reports and Resolutions, 1946-1948 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Press Releases, 1946, 1949, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence and Proposals, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 89)
    - Correspondence and Proposals, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 90)
    - Correspondence and Proposals, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 91)
    - Correspondence and Proposals, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 92)
    - Correspondence and Proposals, 1950-1952, 1958, 1963, 1976, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 93)
    - "Early History of International Christian University" by Morizo Ishidate; untitled brief early history, ca. 1970, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 94)
    - Material Sent to Hachiro Yuasa, 1946, 1949, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 95)
    - Organization Pamphlet in Japanese, 1950, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 96)
    - Fundraising and Historic Files, 1949-1950 (Box 16, Folder 97)
    - Officers; Denominational Members, 1949-1991 (Box 16, Folder 98)
    - Signatures of Famous People, 1949,1950, 1953,1954, 1955,1960, 1963, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 99)
  - JICUF Organization
    - General Procedures: Executive Director, 1954, 1982-1984 (Box 16, Folder 100)
    - Organization of the Foundation; Organization Charts, 1954, 1964, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 101)
    - Staff Appointment Agreement Forms, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 102)
    - Negotiations Between International Christian University and Japan International Christian University Foundation, Inc., 1987 (Box 16, Folder 103)
    - Sub-Committee to Study University Development, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 104)
    - Ad Hoc Committees on Operating Style and Structure, 1968, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 105)
    - Board of Directors - Members and Worksheets, 1966-1975 (Box 17, Folder 106)
    - Board of Directors, 1970-1975 (Box 17, Folder 107)
    - Board of Directors, 1976-1982 (Box 17, Folder 108)
    - Board of Directors, 1983-1991 (Box 17, Folder 109)
    - Board of Directors: General Correspondence, 1984-1988 (Box 17, Folder 110)
    - Search and Planning Committee, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 111)
    - Educational Services Committee, 1976-1980 (Box 17, Folder 112)
    - Men's Committee - Executive Committee Members, 1975-1982 (Box 17, Folder 113)
    - Men's Committee - Chairman's Club, 1976, 1979, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 114)
    - Men's Committee - National Chairman, 1976, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 115)
    - Men's Committee - Sponsors, 1965, 1981, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 116)
    - Women's Planning Committee - Founding Group and Members, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 117)
    - Women's Planning Committee - Executive Committee, 1985, 1988, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 118)
    - Women's Planning Committee - Attendance sheets, 1953-1956 (Box 14, Folder 81)
    - Women's Planning Committee - Projects and Chairmen, 1956-1981 (Box 17, Folder 119)
    - Women's Planning Committee - Local Committee Guidelines, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 120)
    - Women's Planning Committee Donors: Church Groups, Women's Organizations, 1986, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 121)
    - Women's Planning Committee Sponsors, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 122)
    - Legal Correspondence, 1948-1956 (Box 18, Folder 123)
    - Legal Correspondence, 1957-1965 (Box 18, Folder 124)
    - Legal Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 125)
    - Legal Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 18, Folder 126)
    - Legal Correspondence, 1971-1983 (Box 18, Folder 127)
  - JICUF Individual Files
    - JICUF Individual Files: Officers
      - Borton, Hugh - Vice President, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 128)
      - Chen, Daniel Y.C. - Board Member, 1984-1990 (Box 18, Folder 129)
      - Cochran, Raymond - Treasurer, 1985-1991 (Box 18, Folder 130)
      - Cordier, Andrew W. - President, 1968-1975 (Box 33, Folder 258)
      - Diffendorfer, Ralph E. - President, 1949-1951 (Box 33, Folder 259)
      - Gregory, Paul - Vice President, 1971-1977 (Box 18, Folder 132)
      - Gregory, Paul - Vice President, 1978-1980 (Box 19, Folder 133)
      - Gregory, Paul - Vice President, 1981-1983 (Box 19, Folder 134)
      - Gregory, Paul - Vice President, 1984-1986 (Box 19, Folder 135)
      - Gregory, Paul - Vice President, 1987-1990 (Box 19, Folder 136)
      - Gregory, Paul - Vice President, 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 137)
      - Latourette, Kenneth Scott - President (See Also "ICU Leaders"), 1963-1968 (Box 19, Folder 138)
      - MacArthur, Douglas - Honorary Chairman, 1949-1953 (Box 19, Folder 139)
      - Miller, Ruth - Executive Director (See Also under Women's Planning Committee) - Correspondence, 1955-1990 (Box 19, Folder 140)
      - Miller, Ruth - Notes, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 768)
      - Miller, Ruth - Speeches, 1973-1990 (Box 70, Folder 769)
      - Miller, Ruth - Tributes to RM, 1973-1992 (Box 70, Folder 770)
      - Read, David - Biographical Data, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 141)
      - Read, David - Men's Committee Chairman, 1970-1976 (Box 19, Folder 142)
      - Read, David - Men's Committee Chairman, 1976-1990 (Box 19, Folder 143)
      - Read, David - President, 1975-1981 (Box 20, Folder 144)
      - Read, David - President, 1982-1984 (Box 20, Folder 145)
      - Read, David - President, 1985-1991 (Box 20, Folder 146)
      - Smith, John Coventry - Vice President, 1953-1981 (Box 20, Folder 147)
      - Tiller, Carl W. - Executive Committee of the Men's Committee, 1976-1987 (Box 20, Folder 148)
      - Tiller, Carl W. - Treasurer, 1979-1991 (Box 20, Folder 149)
    - JICUF Individual Files: Men's Committee
      - Burke, Coleman - Sponsor, 1955-1990 (Box 20, Folder 150)
      - Chen, Daniel Y.C.- Executive Committee, 1977-1991 (Box 20, Folder 151)
      - Cogswell, James - Chairperson, 1984-1989 (Box 20, Folder 152)
      - Espy, R.H. Edwin - Chairperson, 1976-1990 (Box 21, Folder 153)
      - Germany, C.H. - Vice President Executive Committee, 1972-1990 (Box 21, Folder 154)
      - Jansen, M.B. - Sponsor, 1977-1987 (Box 21, Folder 155)
      - MacArthur, Douglas - Sponsor, 1956-1979 (Box 21, Folder 156)
      - Reischauer, Edwin O. - Sponsor, 1965-1990 (Box 21, Folder 157)
      - Rockefeller, John D., IV, 1958-1969 (Box 21, Folder 158)
      - Rockefeller, John D., IV, 1970-1991 (Box 21, Folder 159)
      - Rockefeller, John D., IV :Clippings, 1966-1984 (Box 22, Folder 160)
      - Rockefeller, John D., IV :Speeches, Biographical Data, 1963-1989 (Box 22, Folder 161)
      - Shriver, Donald - Chairperson, 1983-1989 (Box 22, Folder 162)
      - Smith, John Coventry - Honorary President, 1963-1980 (Box 22, Folder 163)
      - Smith, John Coventry - Honorary President, 1981-1984 (Box 22, Folder 164)
      - Smith, John Coventry, Jr., 1983-1990 (Box 22, Folder 165)
      - Tolley, William P. - Vice President, 1969-1988 (Box 22, Folder 166)
      - Winant, Thomas - Executive Committee, 1977-1987 (Box 22, Folder 167)
    - JICUF Individual Files: Women's Planning Committee
      - Cram, Mary Frances - Vice Chairperson, 1968-1991 (Box 22, Folder 168)
      - Horton, Mildred, 1953-1957 (Box 22, Folder 169)
      - Horton, Mildred, 1958-1987 (Box 22, Folder 170)
      - Hughes, Philippa - Area Chairperson, 1982-1991 (Box 23, Folder 171)
      - Kitadai, Reiko - Vice Chairperson, 1973-1991 (Box 23, Folder 172)
      - Ledden, Henrietta, 1966-1991 (Box 23, Folder 173)
      - Marsh, Margaret, 1965-1991 (Box 23, Folder 174)
      - MacArthur, Jean, 1956-1979 (Box 23, Folder 175)
      - Mowry, Lucetta - Vice Chairperson, 1973-1988 (Box 23, Folder 176)
      - Miller, Ruth - Honorary Chairperson, 1973-1983 (Box 23, Folder 177)
      - Miller, Ruth, 1984-1991 (Box 23, Folder 178)
      - Oka, Yoko - Executive Committee, 1979-1990 (Box 23, Folder 179)